<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[This is new]]></title>
    <link>www.google.com</link>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <generator>Zend_Feed</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX 5S - 285 ltr Refrigerator with FREE STEAM IRON &  Ice Twister and Ice Collector.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/whirlpool-m-mind-30-vx-5s-285-ltr-refrigerator-with-free-steam-iron.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX CRY INOX 5S 285 ltr Double Door Refrigerator is equipped with 6th Sense Tower Cooling and 5 Star Rating. It has Cell fresh Crisper Cover, D-Oxidizer, Carry egg Tray, Bottle Holder, Multi Utility Bin, Freezer Compartment, Ice Twister and Ice Collector. The Image given is only for reference purpose and actual colour/looks may vary from the above Image.

Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX CRY INOX 5S 285 ltr Double Door Refrigerator is equipped with 6th Sense Tower Cooling and 5 Star Rating. It has Cell fresh Crisper Cover, D-Oxidizer, Carry egg Tray, Bottle Holder, Multi Utility Bin, Freezer Compartment, Ice Twister and Ice Collector. The Image given is only for reference purpose and actual colour/looks may vary from the above Image.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Whirlpool Plug-and-Play Refrigerator for Kitcheny</li>
<li>Featured above is a geeky refrigerator inviting women who feel handicap to work in kitchen in absence of gadgets.</li>
<li>Serving dual purpose, this Whirlpool Plug-and-Play refrigerator takes you to an altogether different world which is surrounded by gadgets.</li>
<li>The very plug in of this household accessory would put you across an array of gadgets.</li>
<li>Right on the heels of its &lsquo;centralpark&rsquo; feature,</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/n/i/night_lights_people_party_events_2560x1440_wallpaper_www.wallpaperno.com_1_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Things come alive on the stunning widescreen LED Multi-Touch Apple iPad 2.With WiFi and 3G support, ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/things-come-alive-on-the-stunning-widescreen-led-multi-touch-apple-ipad-2.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Things come alive on the stunning 9.7-inch widescreen LED Multi-Touch display of the Apple iPad 2. With WiFi and 3G support, this 64GB Apple iPad ensures you stay connected to your world all the time. The built-in dual-core A5 chip in this Wi-Fi + 3G iPad facilitates high-end gaming, surfing and overall performance.
Gaming is at a vivid high with up to nine times the graphics performance on this 64GB Apple iPad. Capture immaculate shots in HD with the 0.7 MP front camera of this Wi-Fi iPad, while the secondary 0.3 MP VGA Camera lets you enjoy FaceTime video calling. For an enhanced movie-watching experience, play all your iPad’s digital content wirelessly on HDTV and speakers using AirPlay. Weighing a mere 1.34 lbs, with an amazing 10-hour battery life, Bluetooth 2.1 + EDR technology and more, this Apple iPad 2 is here to become another extension of you.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every year since 2010, there has been a new version of the iPad. In 2012, we've already seen three. One, the iPad Mini, is a different beast altogether.</p>
<p> The new iPad (technically just known as "iPad" at the Apple Store) has a few upgrades, two minor, one significantly major. A Lightning connector replaces the old 30-pin, just like all other new iOS devices this fall. </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Samsung UN55ES8000F 55" LED TV (1920x1080, 240 Hz, HDTV, 3D) With the LED ES8000, experience the next level.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/samsung-un55es8000f-55-led-tv-1920x1080-240-hz-hdtv-3d.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the LED ES8000, experience the next level of Samsung SMART TV technology. Smart Interaction, with Voice Navigation and Gesture Control, allows you to say commands and control TV functions with your hands, while Face Recognition automatically logs you in to App accounts.
 In addition to finding all your favorite shows and movies, you will be able to enjoy the new Signature Services; Family Story, Fitness, and Kids Story. These features are powered by a Dual Core Processor, along with a Built-in camera for Skype and Signature Services.
The Samsung ES8000 Slim LED TV delivers an outstanding home entertainment experience. You can discover the future of smart TV with Smart Interaction1 (Voice Control Face recognition and Motion Control) as well as Smart Hub2 features like Family Story sharing and AllShare Play3 access to compatible devices. Browse the web2 utilise Samsung Apps2 and chat with Skype®4 built-in. Three USB ports mean you can access multiple files and watch your favourite movies with ConnectShare play and USB PVR5.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50,000:1 Dynamic Contrast Ratio delivers deeper blacks and brighter whites through contrast and dimensions</p>
<p>Hisense LED TVs brings you exceptionally vibrant and true-to-life images delivered just as the director imagined</p>
<p>HDMI combines uncompressed digital audio and video signals into a single cable for high-definition sources</p>
<p>Fast response time generates clear motion scenes.</p>
<p>See a clear picture from anywhere in the room with the wide 178° viewing angle</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[As recommended by Elle Magazine, OK!, Zest and much more. 7 audio modules, printable wall planner, 20 golden rules...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/as-recommended-by-elle-magazine-ok-zest-and-much-more.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[No baby food, cereal, cabbage soup or bread free eating with today's deal. That's right people, we've found a way to whip your body into shape by eating like a normal human! ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>One per person.</li>
<li>May buy multiples as gifts.</li>
<li>Voucher valid until 4th April 2013.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Nowadays it's crucial for anyone involved in the music industry to understand 360 deals.which may include any combination.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/nowadays-it-s-crucial-for-anyone-involved-in-the-music-industry-to-understand-360-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Faced with declining sales, the record companies started to think of different ways to make money.  Hence, the 360 deal was born.  With a traditional record deal, 

With a 360 deal, the record company not only produces and releases albums for the artist, they also share in all income the artist generates, which may include any combination of record sales, touring, publishing, and merchandising.  ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>This begs the question: are 360 deals good for artists?  Unfortunately,</li>
<li>the only answer I can give is: it depends.  Traditionally, bands have made the bulk of their income from touring and merchandising,</li>
<li>so allowing the record companies to dip into those income streams doesn't sit well with most artists. </li>
<li>However, there are also some advantages to the 360 model, which I have personally encountered. </li>
<li>For a few years, I managed a band (let's call them "Band X") that had a 360 deal in place.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Beyounic Ski Weekend  curriculum includes four years of English; mathematics through multivariable calculus.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/beyounic-ski-weekend-curriculum-includes-four-years-of-english-mathematics-through-multivariable-calculus.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electives are offered in history, English, math, and the sciences. There is an extensive arts program, with electives in music, theater, and the visual arts, including pottery and photography. 19 Advanced Placement courses are offered for qualified students in English, mathematics, sciences, history, studio art and art history, as well as all three languages taught at the academy.

Students must obtain a minimum of 19 credits for graduation (most four-year students complete 22 to 24 credits), including 4 credits of English, 3 of mathematics, 3 of history, 3 of a foreign language, 2 of science, and 1 of art. The normal academic load is five to six courses per tri-semester.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Electives are offered in history, English, math, and the sciences. There is an extensive arts program, with electives in music, theater, and the visual arts, including pottery and photography. 19 Advanced Placement courses are offered for qualified students in English, mathematics, sciences, history, studio art and art history, as well as all three languages taught at the academy.</p>

<p>Students must obtain a minimum of 19 credits for graduation (most four-year students complete 22 to 24 credits), including 4 credits of English, 3 of mathematics, 3 of history, 3 of a foreign language, 2 of science, and 1 of art. The normal academic load is five to six courses per tri-semester.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Buy Food worth Rs 150 & get 1 Drink Free @ The Good Food Cafe Foodie Delight for You! get the deal...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/buy-food-worth-rs-150-get-1-drink-free-at-the-good-food-cafe-foodie-delight-for-you.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent food safety incidents and the introduction of genetically modified foods in Europe have resulted in an intense public debate regarding the safety of the European food supply. Consumers have little confidence in the safety of their food supply and remain sceptical and distrustful of the management procedures currently in place.

The overall objective of the SAFE FOODS model is to change the scope of decision-making on food safety from single risks to considering foods as sources of risks, benefits and costs that are associated with their production and consumption, and taking into account the social context in which decisions are made ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>One voucher valid for 1 person</li>
<li>One doesn't need to order one food item for Rs 150 but rather total food worth Rs 150 and above</li>
<li>Prior appointment mandatory</li>
<li>Multiple vouchers can be purchased as gifts</li>
<li>Carrying the printout of the voucher is mandatory</li>
<li>Cannot be combined with other existing offers</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$50 worth of Exotic foot massage and spa foot treatment in $30. Cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/50-worth-of-exotic-foot-massage-and-spa-foot-treatment-in-30.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dated bookings are really simple as there are no postage costs and no waiting around for vouchers to arrive. All you need to do is pick your dates, enter your information at checkout and then we'll send you a confirmation email as your proof of booking. It's as easy as 1, 2, 3.
 Good to know Guests must pre-book treatments directly with venue on 01733 234245 at least 2 days prior to arrival to guarantee availability. Any additional treatments should be pre-booked to avoid disappointment and have to be paid directly to the venue. Unless otherwise stated, robes and slippers may incur an additional charge.
All bookings are subject to availability and are non-transferrable. Cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer. Please advise venue of any medical conditions or allergies prior to check-in date.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Overnight stay in a Executive Double or Twin room</li>
<li>Mud Serail Chamber for 2 people (45 mins)</li>
<li>Breakfast included</li>
<li>Full use of spa facilities</li>
<li>Robes and towels provided</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[All-You-Can-Eat Gourmet Pizza + Bottle of Wine or Jug of Beer for 2 People,, you and a friend will feast on all-you-can-eat pizza]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/all-you-can-eat-gourmet-pizza-bottle-of-wine-or-jug-of-beer-for-2-people-at-a-fitzroy-st-favourite-only-27.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We’re all familiar with that feeling of despair that overcomes you when your friend reaches for the last slice of pizza. Suddenly, you realise that it’s all over and that the stray string of cheese that got caught on your collar is all that’s left for you. Feeling pathetic, you lower the pitiful string of cheese into your mouth and wash it down with the dregs of your drink – looks like the booze is gone, too.
Like a very generous person, today’s deal keeps on giving. St Kilda's funkiest little eatery and drinkery is upping the ante and offering you a wining and dining experience that goes on and on until you can consume no more. For just $27, you and a friend will feast on all-you-can-eat pizza at Cushion Lounge! And complete your onslaught of cheesy goodness with a bottle of wine or frosty jug of beer.
A scrumptious selection of pizzas will be yours for the eating, one after another. Cushion Lounge have really outdone themselves today, allowing up to ten Scoopons per booking! Gather your mates, buy a handful of Scoopons and let the feasting begin!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Present printed coupon on arrival</li>
<li>24 hrs' notice required for booking changes/cancellations</li>
<li>Not valid with any other offer</li>
<li>Not valid on Public Holidays</li>
<li>Pizzas must be finished before another can be ordered</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[High Tea with French Champagne! Just $39 for 2 People or $69 for 4 People, and you’ll feel rich with delicious-ness!]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/high-tea-with-french-champagne-just-39-for-2-people-or-69-for-4-people.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[So you might not be an Oscar-winning celebrity jetting around the world in a private plane and holidaying in St Tropez. But that doesn’t mean you can’t get a (delicious) taste of the high life with a truly tempting High Tea!

The dream makers at The Spot Tea Room have got a sensational spread of tasty sweet and savoury morsels ready to delight your tastebuds. From classic ribbon sandwiches to delicate savoury tartlets and yummy homemade cakes, they’ve got it all. Add a selection of premium T2 teas and a glass of fabulous French champagne, and you’ll feel rich with delicious-ness!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So you might not be an Oscar-winning celebrity jetting around the world in a private plane and holidaying in St Tropez. But that doesn’t mean you can’t get a (delicious) taste of the high life with a truly tempting High Tea!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sink Your Teeth into Your Choice of Any Burger – Choose from 13 Big]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/sink-your-teeth-into-your-choice-of-any-burger-choose-from-13-big-juicy-creations.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are some hungers only a burger can satisfy. You can try eating tacos, go to town on parma or scarf down a sausage. But you’ll still be thinking about that juicy patty, those perky buns, that oozing cheese…

Stop drooling, pal! Yank yourself out of your delicious daydreams for a second and get yourself a Mighty Burgers

You give them your Scoopon and they’ll give you two of their perfect burgers, two orders of small chips and two 600ml drinks. You can choose any burger from the menu which means you have 13 scrumptious options. But as long as it’s a burger, it’s guaranteed to calm the rumbling beast in your belly!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Christmas is a pretty great time of year, if only for the fact that you have every excuse to enjoy plate after plate of delicious food. It's after Christmas that isn't so great. That time of year where clothes are strangely tight, mirrors are to be avoided at all costs and the thought of stepping on a set of scales sends a cold shiver up your spine.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Make 2013 a year of fitness with a 12 month gym membership including all classes! ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/make-2013-a-year-of-fitness-with-a-12-month-gym-membership-including-all-classes.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For just $199 get full access to Gymtime Balgowlah, Parcfitness Rose Bay or Parcfitness Bellevue Hill for 12 months (value $1,508). This includes use of all facilities and all calorie-crunching fitness classes! Get into the best shape of your life without contracts and huge fees and get set for the 2013 summer now!

Membership numbers are capped to maintain exclusivity, so you can rest assured that you'll be working out in a private, friendly atmosphere. There are no joining fees, cancellation fees, minimum terms or sneaky contracts – just one great Deal!

Parcfitness is a gym chain situated in the eastern suburbs of Sydney. Between the two great locations, Bellevue Hill and Rose Bay, you'll definitely be able to fit your fitness snugly into your weekly routine. If your days are a little hectic, you can pencil in workouts at any hour of the day or night because the Rose Bay location is open 24/7!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It's open seven days a week, 365 days a year. Access is by swipe card only and free parking is available at the rear of the building for your convenience.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Start the new year with a new you! One hour naturopath consultation to assist]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/start-the-new-year-with-a-new-you-one-hour-naturopath-consultation-to-assist-weight-loss.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CBD Natural Health is a natural medicine practice specialising in health and natural fertility. Located in the heart of Sydney, on Market Street close to the Queen Victoria Building.

The naturopaths at CBD Natural Health offer individual naturopathic treatments that utilise the latest research and information, non-invasive tests and natural medicines to help you achieve effective, lasting results.

Natural therapies are a safe, drug-free and proven way to treat many common conditions including: digestive and bowel complaints, infertility and fertility problems, weight issues, skin problems, sinusitis, fatigue and arthritis.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<P>The naturopaths at CBD Natural Health offer individual naturopathic treatments that utilise the latest research and information, non-invasive tests and natural medicines to help you achieve effective, lasting results.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[10 Fat-Blasting Group Fitness Classes at 5 Fantastic Locations! Only $10 for 1 Person]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/10-fat-blasting-group-fitness-classes-at-5-fantastic-locations-only-10-for-1-person-15-for-2.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nothing gets people moving quite like a calendar.  As the days roll by, the temperature rises and people start shedding layers, we have to assess the damage our hibernation has done… and get our body back before beach season hits!

Kick-start your fitness goals with 10 group fitness classes with Activate Fitness and Lifestyle!

Activate Fitness and Lifestyle really are the transformation experts. Their group personal training sessions make sure working out isn’t a chore and a client-centred approach means they’re committed to helping you turn excess baggage into trim, toned and terrific! Best of all, a variety of workout routines means that you’re attacking calories and wobbly bits from all angles. ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Get the Sexy Summer Bod You’ve Always Wanted and Achieve Your New Year’s Resolutions with 10 Group Fitness Classes at Your Choice of 5 Great Locations – Carlton, Essendon, North Essendon, Maribyrnong and Greenvale! Attend When and Where You Want and Transform Your Body in a Motivating Team Environment! Up to $400 Value!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Return radiance with 70 minutes of pampering: blueberry facial, eye treatment, body scrub ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/return-radiance-with-70-minutes-of-pampering-blueberry-facial-eye-treatment-body-scrub.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Body Temple Spa is a beauty and spa business focusing on skin revision with a holistic approach to their treatments. They are known for their expertise on non-surgical facelifts and advanced skin treatment technology using cosmeceutical products.

The team at The Body Temple Spa comprises of a cosmetic doctor, celebrity therapist and expert dermal therapists. Owner and celebrity therapist, Thez, has over 20 years clinical experience, having graduated as a medical technologist in pathology, BA in Science, DIP in advanced skin therapy. She went on to specialise in dermal therapy, covering pre and post preparation surgical procedure. She is a qualified trainer and assessor with international experience. Her tailor-made approach to treatment is to integrate her medical knowledge and bring a truly holistic solution to each individual.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be treated with a dry body scrub to remove skin cells, followed by a nourishing body souffle to hydrate and nourish dry skin (value $120).</p>
<p>Complete the treatment with a facial masque and body wrap while enjoying a soothing scalp massage (value $30).Owner and celebrity therapist, Thez, has over 20 years clinical experience.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[1 Hour Relaxation Massage or 1 Hour Deep Tissue Full Body Massage in Docklands – Only $29 for One Person]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/1-hour-relaxation-massage-or-1-hour-deep-tissue-full-body-massage-in-docklands-only-29-for-one-person.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perfectly located in Docklands, the magical masseurs at Healthy Palace are standing by to ease muscle pain, relieve tension and soothe your body from top to toe.

You’ll enjoy the ultimate tension release with your choice of two deliciously relaxing massages. Revive your tired and achy body and target knotted muscles with a Deep Tissue Massage. Or surrender your stresses to a Relaxation Massage designed to soothe joints and muscles and awaken your body's energy flow. Whichever you choose, you'll realise you've discovered the perfect antidote to the stresses of work - heavenly Healthy Palace.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Work stress and tension have a sneaky way of following you home and worming their way into your neck, back and shoulders. Leave your worries and woes in the city where they belong and chill out with an hour of full body massage before you hit the sanctuary of home</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The Black Pearl Restaurant Dining experience at The Majestic Black Pearl restaurant ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/the-black-pearl-restaurant-dining-experience-at-the-majestic-black-pearl-restaurant.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Black Pearl has an interesting and chequered history which dates as far back as 1909. Built in Pukavik in Sweden, and destined to be one of the last servicers of the wooden trading schooners, she was originally named the ‘Black Opal’

Fashioned on strength, so that she could penetrate the Baltic cold winters and sail in the strong Nordic winds of Scandinavia, the Black Schonner was constructed with a hull of two layers of thick seasoned oak. Over one hundred and fifty feet long, with three stout masts rising ninty feet from the deck, the ‘Black Opal’ must have made a majestic sight indeed as she sailed the high seas on her trading missions carrying a net weight of nearly four hundred tonnes.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Booking required. 21316000</li>
<li>Blackout dates: 14 February 2013</li>
<li>Voucher is for 1 person and can be used between Tuesday and Saturday for dinner.</li>
<li>Pre booking is required and please inform that you're using a DealToday voucher.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ A romantic day together at the Fortina Spa, where complete relaxation and luxury is the key to the perfect day]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/a-romantic-day-together-at-the-fortina-spa-where-complete-relaxation-and-luxury-is-the-key-to-the-perfect-day.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fortina Spa – The relaxing Spa environment is a complete change from the everyday stress of life and offers total relaxation to release tension, lift the spirit and enhance that ‘feel good’ factor we all crave. Within the vast area of the Spa there are three additional spa facilities namely Spa Sante, Belle Époque Beauty Centre and the Hypogeum all designed to leave you feeling refreshed, revitalised and recharged.

Chinese and Thai Cuisine has won four awards in the last few years. Can Thai at the Fortina Spa Resort uses only the finest quality ingredients brought in from around the world to offer you the most authentic, great tasting dishes on the Island. Can Thai brings together an exquisite combination of Cantonese and Thai cuisine, with very welcoming Asian staff and the tropical ambience of the tropical gardens which surround this restaurant. It’s the ideal place to dine in a romantic setting.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Booking required. 2346 2149
You must state your intention to utilize the voucher on booking
Black out days from 23rd Dec 2012 to 3rd Jan 2013
Cannot be used in conjunction with any other special offer, discount or membership scheme
Beverages are not included in the restaurant
USDA Steaks and Lobster dishes are not included
Parking is not included in this deal
Limited to 25 deals per person
Opening Times:
Fortina Spa Open from 9am – 7pm daily
Spa Sante Open from 2pm – 6pm weekdays and from 10am – 6pm on weekends & public holidays
Taste Open for Lunch from Tuesday to Sunday
Can Thai Open for lunch from Thursday to Tuesday

Limit of 25 deals per person.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Les Miserables: Highlights From the Motion Picture Soundtrack by Anne Dudley, Anne Dudley (Musical Producer), Anne Dudley]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/les-miserables-highlights-from-the-motion-picture-soundtrack-by-anne-dudley-anne-dudley-musical-producer-anne-dudley.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Editorial Reviews Barnes & Noble Les Misérables is the motion-picture adaptation of the beloved global stage sensation seen by more than 60 million people in 42 countries and in 21 languages around the globe and still breaking box-office records everywhere in its 28th year. Helmed by The King's Speech's Academy Award®-winning director,  

Tom Hooper, the Working Title/Cameron Mackintosh production stars Hugh Jackman, Oscar® winner Russell Crowe, Anne Hathaway, Amanda Seyfried, Eddie Redmayne, Aaron Tveit, Samantha Barks, with Helena Bonham Carter and Sacha Baron Cohen.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[</p>Valid for a one-year (twelve month) Premium Subscription to FIT Radio • Visit www.fitradio.com for more information • Other conditions apply</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Pay $ 50 for Facial, Bleach, Hair Pack for Hair Strengthening, Hair Wash & @ Orange Family Beauty Salon]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/pay-50-for-facial-bleach-hair-pack-for-hair-strengthening-hair-wash-at-orange-family-beauty-salon.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ambiance at the spa is very soothing with tastefully done up interiors which transport its guests immediately into relaxation mode. Fine detailing has been taken into account with the artifacts which have been handpicked from Thailand giving the Spa the ultimate Thai touch.

Lanna is host to a bouquet of rejuvenating and relaxing therapies with variations in the massage techniques and durations, ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Offer includes: 20% off on full boy therapies, thai foot reflexology or express therapies</li>
<li>See below for services on offer</li>
<li>Valid for both men and women</li>
<li>No cross gender services available</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/b/o/bokeh_photography_03_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Samsung Black ST201 Digital Camera with 16.1 Megapixels and 10x Optical Zoom]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/samsung-black-st201-digital-camera-with-16-1-megapixels-and-10x-optical-zoom.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Find the best deals for electronics at dealspl.us! Select from a broad range of electronics discounts, specials, sales and other offers suggested by our community

The Nikon D5100 offers a host of new photographic and video tools that deliver superior performance and exceptional image quality with surprising versatility. With 16.2 megapixels, a swivel Vari-Angle LCD monitor, full HD movie capabilities, new EFFECTS Mode and new HDR setting, you hold the power and performance to capture beautiful moments and the freedom to get creative.
]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>16.1 megapixel resolution with high-quality still images and video recordings<br />Featuring Auto, Scene Modes, 720p HD Movie Recording, Face Detection Technology and Optical Image Stabilization</li>
<li>Samsung 4.85-48.5mm zoom lens with 10x optical zoom<br />Equivalent to a 27-270mm lens on an analog camera with TTL Multi AF, Center AF, Tracking AF, Face-Detection AF, Smart Face Recognition AF, Glass Lens</li>
<li>3.0" TFT LCD screen with image editing features<br />Featuring color TFT LCD screen</li>
<li>Built-in flash with Red-Eye Reduction, Fill-In Flash, Auto On/Off and Slow-Sync Flash</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_37__1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Dryer Vent 38" Vac Vacuum Hose Attachment Lint Dust Laundry Cleaner]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/dryer-vent-38-vac-vacuum-hose-attachment-lint-dust-laundry-cleaner.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[f you can keep the tube straight, and you have a not so strong vacuum, it would work ideally, so that's why I gave 4. But I could not get it down to the bottom of dryer, and I had hard time keeping the tube straight and open for optimum air flow. it's a good idea, but I think it needs more quality control testing. Maybe, those old retractable plastic tubes that washing machines used to drain water with. it's thinner material, and doesn't squeeze closed with air suction.
]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Reduces fire risk and drying time </li>
<li>Extends the life of your dryer </li>
<li>Slide one end over vacuum hose </li>
<li>The other end suctions lint and dust from hard to reach places </li>
<li>Hose is 38 inches long </li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_65__1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Waring DF55 Professional Mini 1-2/7-Pound-Capacity Stainless-Steel Deep Fryer]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/waring-df55-professional-mini-1-2-7-pound-capacity-stainless-steel-deep-fryer.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The machine's user-friendly control panel makes it easy to adjust the heat up to 375 degrees F, while its powerful 1500-watt immersion-style heating element provides fast heat-up and recovery times. Simply add up to 1-2/7 pounds of food to the heavy mesh frying basket, then lower it into the hot oil using the cool-touch handle for safety. Batches of French fries, battered onion rings, doughnuts, and more come out fried to crispy perfection--just lift the basket to drain. 


Other thoughtful design details include "power" and "ready" indicator lights, a 2-quart enamel-coated oil container with a pouring spout, stabilizing feet, and stay-cool lid, basket, and side handles. When finished, the lid, oil container, and detachable basket handle clean up easily by hand or in the dishwasher. Attractively housed in brushed stainless steel, the mini deep fryer measures 14 by 10-1/5 by 11-4/5 inches.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Stainless-steel deep fryer with 1-2/7-pound food capacity</li>
<li>1500-watt immersion-style heating element for fast results</li>
<li>2-quart oil container; adjustable heat; "power" and "ready" indicators</li>
<li>Heavy mesh frying basket; stay-cool handles; dishwasher-safe parts</li>
<li>Measures 14 by 10-1/5 by 11-4/5 inches</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_112_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ Pinstripes takes power-packed aisles of New York International Bank and the sharpest of its minds. ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/pinstripes-takes-power-packed-aisles-of-new-york-international-bank-and-the-sharpest-of-its-minds.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Devil in Pinstripes takes power-packed aisles of New York International Bank and the sharpest of its minds. It is the story of Amit, an ambitious MBA who joins NYIB and thereby, the world of high pressure competitive foreign banking and the current crisis that engulfs this sector. 

 Free shipping will be done in India,
Delivery will be done within 3-4 days from the date of purchase,
The product is marketed by sample.com

]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Taxes Included</li>
<li>One voucher valid for one person only</li>
<li>Orders taken by email, post or telephone</li>
<li>We will confirm your order and advise shipping costs</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_100_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[SuperBookDeals: The Leader in Global Marketplace eCommerce]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/superbookdeals-the-leader-in-global-marketplace-ecommerce.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SuperBookDeals (a Far Corner Company) is a 20-year-old, US-based company. It is one of the largest sellers of books, DVDs, and CDs through nearly two dozen global marketplaces including Amazon, Half.com, and eBay as well as its own site. The company delivers the highest level of services possible to millions of customers annually, 

offering the most extensive catalog of almost twenty million products in both new and used conditions. Fulfilling orders in five different currencies, ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Offers millions of Books, DVDs, and CDs for sale,</li>
<li>Supports relationships with hundreds of vendors worldwide to ensure the largest selection possible,</li>
<li>Constantly scans the world supply chain for opportunities to lower prices,</li>
<li>Sells books in 27 different languages,</li>
<li>Ships almost three million orders per year,</li>
<li>Analyzes its prices almost 300 million times per day,</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_130_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Schaum's Outline of French Grammar (Schaum's Outlines) (Paperback)]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/schaum-s-outline-of-french-grammar-schaum-s-outlines-paperback.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Short Description for Schaum's Outline of French Grammar

Offers a review of French grammar, with exercises, quick drills, and verb charts. This title includes various usages and explains grammatical topics.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Publisher: Schaum Outline Series</li>
<li>Format: Paperback 408 pages</li>
<li>Categories: Usage & Grammar Guides Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework Grammar & Vocabulary Study & Learning Skills: General</li>
<li>Published: 01 November 20012</li>
<li>See: Full bibliographic data</li>
<li>Sales rank: 1,543</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_115_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The English Language and Linguistics Companion (Palgrave Student Companions) (Paperback)]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/the-english-language-and-linguistics-companion-palgrave-student-companions-paperback.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interested in discovering how language works? Daunted by the prospect of studying linguistics at university? "The English Language

inguistics Companion "is a tool-kit for the novice linguist. Integrating study skills with substantive coverage," "it offers an innovative approach to the study of English language and linguistics, helping students see how their chosen discipline 'fits together'.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Publisher: Palgrave MacMillan</li>
<li>Format: Paperback 384 pages</li>
<li>Categories: Language: Reference & General Linguistics</li>
<li>Published: 25 May 201</li>
<li>See: Full bibliographic data</li>
<li>ISBN 13: 9781403989710 </li>
<li>Sales rank: 60,799</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$33.50 & up - 2-for-1 Tickets to Broadway Shows.Broadway Week offers the best savings of the year on 19 Broadway shows]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/33-50-up-2-for-1-tickets-to-broadway-shows-broadway-week-offers-the-best-savings-of-the-year-on-19-broadway-shows.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For two weeks only, 19 Broadway shows are offering the best savings of the year. Get two tickets for the price of one for any of the participating plays and musicals during Broadway Week, 

Rarely discounted productions, Tony winners and long-running Broadway favorites are all part of the mix, with tickets starting at $33.50 each (regularly $67]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul><li>Broadway Week offers the best savings of the year on 19 Broadway shows</li><li>Select seats are 2 for the price of 1 and start at $33.50 per ticket</li><li>For an additional $20, many shows are offering upgraded seating locations</li><li>2 weeks of performances are available, Jan. 22 - Feb. 7</li><li>Promo code <b>BWAYWEEK</b> is required; please see "Fine Print" for booking instructions</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$17 - NYC: Secret Spy Exhibit in Times Square, Reg. $35. Tickets are $13-$17, regularly $27.13-$35.30, including all fees]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/17-nyc-secret-spy-exhibit-in-times-square-reg-35-tickets-are-13-17-regularly-27-13-35-30-including-all-fees.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Secret World of Espionage," an interactive, family-friendly exhibit in Times Square, will take you beyond the Hollywood fiction and put you face-to-face with the secret truth that goes on behind the scenes. With this offer, tickets to the exhibit are more than 50% off.

At the exhibit, visitors can encounter real declassified gadgets from the world's leading intelligence agencies, navigate their way through an actual laser field, create their own disguise and alter their voices, and explore more than 200 historicall artifacts illustrating the evolution of spy technology.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vouchers may be redeemed now through March 15, 2013. To redeem, bring a printed voucher to the Discovery Times Square box office. Limit 8 vouchers per person. Discounts reflect TSX Operating Co.’s current ticket prices. Full prices may differ on the day of the event. This deal cannot be combined with any other offers. Must be used in 1 visit. <br></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$30 - Tony Winner 'Anything Goes' at Golden Gate Theatre.The New York Times calls it "musical-comedy joy" and USA]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/30-tony-winner-anything-goes-at-golden-gate-theatre-the-new-york-times-calls-it-musical-comedy-joy-and-usa-today-calls-it-glorious.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent production of Cole Porter's "Anything Goes" won the Tony Award for Best Revival of a Musical in 2011. Travelzoo subscribers can see this Broadway classic at SHN Golden Gate Theatre in San Francisco and save more than 40% on tickets, starting at $30 (reg. $50).

The New York Times calls it "musical-comedy joy" and USA Today calls it "glorious" and "exuberant." 

In "Anything Goes," a group of passengers are in for a bumpy ride and lots of romantic complications when they climb aboard an ocean liner. The musical first debuted on Broadway in 1934, and many of its songs are now standards -- "I Get a Kick Out of You," "It's De-Lovely" and, of course, "Anything Goes."
]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Full booking instructions are below. No promo code is needed when booking online. Fees of $10 per ticket are included in the ticket price. $5 per order will be additional. Tickets subject to availability. Offer not valid on previously purchased tickets. Offer may be discontinued at any time. No refunds, cancellations or exchanges.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sony have introduced the Xperia E as a new entry-level handset with HD Voice plus data and power-saving tools for new smartphone users.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/sony-have-introduced-the-xperia-e-as-a-new-entry-level-handset-with-hd-voice-plus-data-and-power-saving-tools-for-new-smartphone-users.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Xperia E puts one thing above all else, voice calls; a function that obviously predates when the ‘smart’ came to smartphones, but nevertheless, one of the most important features of any phone and something that recent devices have seemed to place on the back burner somewhat. 

The Sony Xperia E is one of the most affordable handsets to feature HD Voice and provided you’re on a network and calling a handset which both support the service, calls are said to be significantly more crystal then what we’ve come to expect from the average phone call, both when speaking and listening.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sony’s new low-cost handset doesn’t simply revolve around HD Voice of course, it also has a full suite of Sony Mobile features, services and apps, not to mention a similar design language to more premium handsets such as the Sony Xperia J and special tools designed to ease those users new to smartphones into the Sony ecosystem.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Break The Limits Of Slim With LG Blade 14.0 (35.8 CMS) HD LED LCD NOTEBOOK. With trendsetting slim styles.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/break-the-limits-of-slim-with-lg-blade-14-0-35-8-cms-hd-led-lcd-notebook-with-trendsetting-slim-styles-that-never-sacrifice-speed-or-power.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[trendsetting slim styles that never sacrifice speed or power, LG laptops have the latest state-of-the-art designs and features. With the best combination of performance for size, 
as well as cutting-edge technology in display and sound that sets new standards in entertainment – LG notebooks and laptops pack a serious 3D punch for 3D games, movies or graphics. Find your laptop or notebook and be sure to see all of our computer products and accessories.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seize your smart style with LG Blade that integrates our slimmests design with new and innovative technologies. Every angle is sliced slimmer from its super slim 4.5mm LED LCD to its 10mm super slim Bezel that’s packed within the metallic 23.8 mm body. The trendsetting slim style never sacrifices speed or power as it offers the best combination of performance or size. Join the slim innovation with the sharp styled LG Blade.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Experience The Superior Sound On The Road.Direct FM/CD Audio Recording to USB Now record your favorite songs]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/experience-the-superior-sound-on-the-road-direct-fm-cd-audio-recording-to-usb-now-record-your-favorite-songs-playing-from-fm.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Easy & Simple Plug and Play. LG Head units have a built-in Front Audio Aux in, for connection to portable music players and other external devices. Just a single connection to make listening more convenient.

Extreme Dynamic Sound System It can increase the low and high range sound so that the listener can experience dynamic powerful sound by simply pushing the XDSS button. In addition, XDSS Plus, which is LG's premium sound effect, gives listeners deeper and stronger low range sound.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You do not need any more annoying cables to listen to music from the smart phones in your car. Just download Wics Apps to your smart phones , and music files in your smart phones will be played from your car speakers.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/delicious-cocktails-don-t-have-to-be-alcoholic-whether-you-re-catering-for-a-guest-who-is-driving-home-or-you-simply-feel-like-something-lighter.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home or you simply feel like something lighter, here are a few recipe ideas for some delicious and healthy non-alcoholic drinks.

Place the blueberries and hulled strawberries in a liquidiser and a little tonic water. Blend until smooth then top up with the remaining tonic water. Serve over ice, if preferred.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>150ml tomato juice</li>
<li>Tabasco sauce</li>
<li>Worcestershire sauce</li>
<li>Fresh lemon juice</li>
<li>Celery salt and pepper</li>
<li>To garnish, a stick of celery and a wedge of lime</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Your local Morrisons Pharmacy is a great place to pick up friendly, expert advice for quitting smoking.Your local Morrisons Pharmacy is a great place...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/your-local-morrisons-pharmacy-is-a-great-place-to-pick-up-friendly-expert-advice-for-quitting-smoking-your-local-morrisons-pharmacy-is-a-great-place.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The best plan of action for giving up is to pick a quit date and stick to it. Make sure you have plenty of distractions in place to take your mind off your cigarettes.

Only 3% of smokers are able to stop without the help of pharmacists like ours. We can offer a variety of nicotine replacement options to help you kick the habit.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Reduce the risk of stroke, heart disease and cancer.</li>
<li>Protect people around you from passive smoking.</li>
<li>Save money – one pack of 20 cigarettes a day costs more than £2,000 a year.</li>
<li>Breathing becomes easier and food and drink tastes better.</li>
<li>You’ll look fresher as the tar in cigarettes can stain your skin and teeth.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Boston Market also still has a coupon for $1 off a $10 purchase, good until Feb.  You can get your coupon from this website]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/boston-market-also-still-has-a-coupon-for-1-off-a-10-purchase-good-until-feb-you-can-get-your-coupon-from-this-website.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Boston Market, known as Boston Chicken until 1995, headquartered in Golden, Colorado, is a chain of American fast casual restaurants. It is owned by private equity firm Sun Capital Partners, headquartered in Boca Raton, Florida. Boston Market has its greatest presence in the Northeastern United States. As of August 2007, the chain has 530 company-owned restaurants locations in 28 ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The new sweepstakes has been launched to help promote their incredible $10 deal and we have all of the details on the fabulous prizes that could be yours! Any customer who decides to play will have a chance to win one of three $10,000 checks.</p><p> They’ll also have a chance to win other prizes, although those prizes have not yet been revealed.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Go color crazy. Changing your hair can totally transform you; it's exhilarating, exciting and gives you an instant confidence boost.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/go-color-crazy-changing-your-hair-can-totally-transform-you-it-s-exhilarating-exciting-and-gives-you-an-instant-confidence-boost.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If you want a quick change or you're keen to experiment with an array of hair colors before you take the plunge to permanent, this gives you the freedom to do so thanks to its wash-in, wash-out properties. Available in rinses, shampoos and sprays, you don't even have to book yourself into a salon for a temporary dye job.

Unlike the more permanent options, these products don't contain any ammonia. This means the hair shaft isn't opened up and so the color clings to your hair, rather than being absorbed by it, which is why the color will simply wash out after shampooing.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<li>Reduce the risk of stroke, heart disease and cancer.</li>
<li>Protect people around you from passive smoking.</li>
<li>Save money – one pack of 20 cigarettes a day costs more than £2,000 a year.</li>
<li>Breathing becomes easier and food and drink tastes better.</li>
<li>You’ll look fresher as the tar in cigarettes can stain your skin and teeth.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Those old skin cells are weighing you down. A body exfoliation treatment is a gentle way of sloughing off the dead skin and all those other nasties on the outside and letting your fresh, clear skin show through]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/those-old-skin-cells-are-weighing-you-down-a-body-exfoliation-treatment-is-a-gentle-way-of-sloughing-off-the-dead-skin-and-all-those-other-nasties-on-the-outside-and-letting-your-fresh-clear-skin-show-through.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are lots of different body scrubs available; some use granular mixtures like salt-scrub, sugar-scrub or wheat bran, while others concentrate on deep hydration, to soften up the dead skin cells, before rubbing you down with a special, slightly abrasive cloth.

If you want peachy skin all over, you'll need to take your clothes off – though, most spas will provide you with a pair of disposable undies to preserve your modesty. The scrub is applied in circular motions to tease out any dirt from your pores. It's also often combined with a massage, to help boost your circulation and to give your skin the maximum healthy glow.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A body exfoliation treatment takes no prisoners when it comes to dull skin, problem patches and clogged pores. If you're feeling a bit flaky or grubby it's a relaxing, refreshing way to beautify yourself.</p>

<p>For sensitive souls who suffer from particularly bad eczema or skin conditions such as psoriasis, a body scrub might be too abrasive.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The piscatorial pedicure process varies from region to region but essentially, it involves immersing your feet into a tub of warm water filled with about 100 tiny toothless carp called gurra rufa.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/the-piscatorial-pedicure-process-varies-from-region-to-region-but-essentially-it-involves-immersing-your-feet-into-a-tub-of-warm-water-filled-with-about-100-tiny-toothless-carp-called-gurra-rufa.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The piscatorial pedicure process varies from region to region but essentially, it involves immersing your feet into a tub of warm water filled with about 100 tiny toothless carp called gurra rufa. A native Turkish fish, also referred to doctor fish, thrive in warm water and live off anything available – including dead, flaking skin. They don't have teeth so whilst calluses and other stubborn ailments are gnawed at, healthy skin is left untouched.

After 15 to 30 minutes of acting as human fish food, you'll be asked to remove your fresh-water feet from the tank and you'll be treated to a more standardized pedicure, made easier by the soft skin the fish doctors leaves behind. This will usually consist of a foot massage and scrub followed by a nail trimming and toe polishing if so required.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The unorthodox treatment was adapted from Turkish techniques and is a natural alternative to potentially unsanitary razors, clippers or pumice stones. In countries where fish pediís are popular, people often soak their whole bodies in baths full of fish.

Any fear you might have about the hungry fish should dissolve into fits of laughter as the treatment is described as having more of a ticking sensation rather than anything painful. Some even draw a comparison to your feet falling asleep and if you can get past the fact that fish are snacking on your tootsies, you might just end up with the best pedicure of your life.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Martial arts is an all-encompassing term for any set of structured fighting and defence techniques, although it is now most commonly associated with Asian combat styles.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/martial-arts-is-an-all-encompassing-term-for-any-set-of-structured-fighting-and-defence-techniques-although-it-is-now-most-commonly-associated-with-asian-combat-styles.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Martial arts is an all-encompassing term for any set of structured fighting and defence techniques, although it is now most commonly associated with Asian combat styles. Training methods will vary depending on the discipline, but will typically include learning set routines composed of techniques known as forms or kata.

Testing has also become an important part of the martial arts discipline and is used as a way of monitoring progress and achievement. By picking up different techniques and mastering them, you can work your way through recognised skill sets, known as ‘grades’, which represent your level of expertise. Completion of each graded testing is accompanied by the attainment of different coloured belts. Your current skill level is therefore represented by the belt you used to tie your robes; the lowest level (beginner) is represented by a white belt in many martial arts, whereas more experienced martial artists possess black and brown belts. Tests normally require you to complete one or more katas, answer some questions or complete some simple physical exercises, and may also include sparring.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some teachers also place more of an emphasis on the holistic capabilities of martial arts. Training could boost your self-esteem, confidence, self-control and become an important way of releasing the stresses and strains of daily life. Nothing beats that old trick of picturing someone’s face as you hit something</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Ashtanga yoga is good for weight loss, flexibility, circulation and strength, and because you spend time focusing on your posture and breathing]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/ashtanga-yoga-is-good-for-weight-loss-flexibility-circulation-and-strength-and-because-you-spend-time-focusing-on-your-posture-and-breathing.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By synchronizing all of these movements with your breathing, it's no surprise that your body starts to produce an intense internal heat and it's this rise in temperature that purifies muscles and organs and expels those unwanted toxins. According to the teachings of Pattabhi Jois, one of the first known Ashtanga yoga practitioners, the hormones and minerals which are released when the body perspires subsequently nourish the body when the sweat is absorbed back into the skin (yummy).

At the core of Ashtanga yoga you'll find deep and even breathing. Teachers of the practice claim that when you regulate your breathing, each move should become easier to perform. It also ensures better circulation of the blood, so you'll be left feeling as light as a feather but with a body as strong as an ox.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People of all ages, mobility and fitness levels can benefit from yoga as it's a holistic discipline with a low risk of injury. It can help to relieve stress, high blood pressure and insomnia because it relaxes you and because you feel less stressed and irritable, your mood will be lifted and can help get rid of that little black cloud that's been following you around.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Interior design online is an online retailer with no physical showroom. Shop when you want, saving time...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/interior-design-online-is-an-online-retailer-with-no-physical-showroom-shop-when-you-want-saving-time-money-and-with-confidence-that-all-items.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interior design online is an online resource to assist you in decorating your unique space. Designer furniture and accessories without the designer price tag delivered right to your door.
Interior design online brings together an extensive range of designer furniture, lighting and décor accessories. Our products can be viewed across several different decorating styles to help work in with your existing décor or to create a completely new look.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>the recommended retail price, with free delivery on some items. </p><p>Interior design online is an online retailer with no physical showroom.</p><p> Shop when you want, saving time, money and with confidence that all items on our site are from quality New Zealand suppliers.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Pay $19 to get 25% off on ticket from HOHO Travel Service. Explore the city like never before! The tour covers all famous monuments, museums and marketsPay $19 to get 25% off on ticket from HOHO Travel Service. Explore the city like never before! The tour]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/pay-rs-19-to-get-25-off-on-ticket-from-hoho-bus-service-explore-the-city-like-never-before-the-tour-covers-all-famous-monuments-museums-and-markets.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Looking for an option to take a break from your monotonous routine and busy schedule to revive and refresh? how about seeing true colours of Delhi with utmost comfort, convenience and at a pocket friendly cost? Explore the vivacious, 

multihued and versatile culture of India. HOHO Bus Service lets you enjoy a family outing and Delhi sightseeing in a comfy, AC bus for a pocket friendly price. Now, you can explore the rustic charm of Old Delhi, relish culinary delights, shop for artifacts and souvenirs and soak in the culture of the city, all at once! Pay $ 19 to get 25% off on ticket from HOHO Bus Service. Explore the city like never before!]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
 <li>Offer includes: <b>25% off on sightseeing tour tickets</b></li><li>The tour covers all famous monuments, museums and markets</li>
<li><b>See below for routes</b></li>
<li>Every bus has a 'guest relations executive' to provide information about the sights</li>
<li>HOHO boasts of an international presence and operates in London, Rome, New York, Sydney, Barcelona and other cities across the globe</li><li>Get Travel at their all boarding (pick up/drop) points every 45 minutes (starting 8:30 am)</li><li>Call at HOHO Bus customer care between 2:00 pm to 5:00 pm and 6:30 pm to 8:30 pm</li><li>Applicable taxes included</li>        </ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_139_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[A superb holiday offer! Pay $52 to enjoy 4D/3N couple stay worth $85  with United Lifestyles Pvt Ltd.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/a-superb-holiday-offer-pay-52-to-enjoy-4d-3n-couple-stay-worth-85-with-united-lifestyles-pvt-ltd.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Call at 1231456789 or mail at info@test.in with necessary details (name, age, contact no, preferred dates of visiting, place of visit and mydala voucher code) for booking.

A superb holiday offer! Pay Rs. 3333 to enjoy 4D/3N couple stay worth Rs. 4444 with United Lifestyles Pvt Ltd.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
        <li>Offer includes: 4D/3N stay</li><li>Accommodation on twin sharing basis</li><li>Simple booking procedure, see below</li><li>Applicable taxes included</li>        </ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_31__1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$25 -- 10-Nt Bangkok & Phuket Break w/Flights & More for 2. Visit Bangkok and Phuket on this 10-day Thailand package from ME Travel for just $2599 ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/25-10-nt-bangkok-phuket-break-w-flights-more-for-2-visit-bangkok-and-phuket-on-this-10-day-thailand-package-from-me-travel-for-just-2599.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visit Bangkok and Phuket on this 10-day Thailand package from ME Travel for just $2599 for two people including flights from Perth. This deal will save you $1093 off what you would usually pay.

Departures from Sydney, Melbourne and Brisbane are also available for just $2799 for two people. Children aged 2-11 can travel for just $950 per child while single travelers will pay just $1750 departing from Perth and $1850 from Sydney, Melbourne and Brisbane.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vouchers must be purchased by 23 January but could sell out before. Child vouchers are not inclusive of spa treatment. When you are ready to book, contact ME travel at info@metravel.com.au and mention your Travelzoo voucher. Vouchers can be redeemed for stays from 13 March to 14 September.<br><br><b>Blackout dates: </b>28-31 March; 1-21 April; 23-30 June; 1-13 July. All tax is included. Vouchers are not refundable and cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer or promotion. Once you have booked your holiday with ME Travel, no cancellations are permitted or your voucher is subject to forfeiture.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_56_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Visit Bangkok and Phuket on this 10-day Thailand package from ME Travel for just $77 for two people including flights from Perth.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/visit-bangkok-and-phuket-on-this-10-day-thailand-package-from-me-travel-for-just-77-for-two-people-including-flights-from-perth.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Departures from Sydney, Melbourne and Brisbane are also available for just $2799 for two people.

The official 5-star Pathumwan Princess Hotel has won multiple awards including a 2012 World Luxury Hotel Award and a Certificate of Excellence from TripAdvisor. ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vouchers must be purchased by 23 January but could sell out before. Child vouchers are not inclusive of spa treatment. When you are ready to book, contact ME travel and mention your Travelzoo voucher. Vouchers can be redeemed for stays from 13 March to 14 September.<br><br><b>Blackout dates: </b>28-31 March; 1-21 April; 23-30 June; 1-13 July. All tax is included. Vouchers are not refundable and cannot be used in conjunction with any other offer or promotion. Once you have booked your holiday with ME Travel, no cancellations are permitted or your voucher is subject to forfeiture.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/d/e/deal_109_.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Tantalize your Taste Buds! Get flat Rs 250 off on Minimum Bill of Rs 500 & above @ Coriander Leaf.Get flat 20% off.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/tantalize-your-taste-buds-get-flat-rs-250-off-on-minimum-bill-of-rs-500-above-at-coriander-leaf-get-flat-20-off.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Best Hand-Picked Restaurant Deals: updated daily by our team of coupon clippers and deal finders. Every deal is hand-selected by our team. We're always adding new brands based on user feedback.

Dining Deals is a free, top-reviewed coupons app that gives you the best deals for your favorite restaurants.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
	<li>Taxes extra</li>
	<li>One voucher allowed per bill</li>
	<li>Redeem the voucher in one month</li>
	<li>Redeem the voucher in a single visit</li>
	<li>Can purchase multiple vouchers for gifting</li>
	<li>For any queries. Call 0172-4511100,4511101, 4511102</li>
	<li>Multiple vouchers allowed</li>
	<li>Show the voucher printout/SMS at the outlet.</li>
	<li>Cannot be redeemed with cash.</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Crazzzy Deal at Crazzzy Price! Hit the deal by paying just $ 20 for a comfort 1N/2D stay worth $ 40 at france]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/crazzzy-deal-at-crazzzy-price-hit-the-deal-by-paying-just-20-for-a-comfort-1n-2d-stay-worth-40-at-france-114.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being in Paharganj which is france upscale location, the Hotel is very close to the famous Cannaught Place Market. It has easy approach to all the embassies. Other famous shopping centers that are quite close are Rajouri Garden, Food Courts, Food Courts,
The hotel provides facilities and comforts of International standards with 100% clean and hygienic rooms with high-quality amenities.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Voucher Valid Till 31st MARCH 2013.
One voucher is valid for two People.
Stay of one child up to 5 years of age is complementary (without extra bed).
Prior booking in advance is mandatory.
Pickup and Drop will on Prior request only.
Multiple vouchers can be brought for extended stay.
All booking confirmations are subjected to availability.
Once the booking is done, no cancellation requests will be entertained under any circumstances.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>All Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/a/r/architecture_room_interior_designs_marble_limestone_1920x1200_wallpaper_www.wallpaperno.com_1_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
