<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[ Feeds]]></title>
    <link>www.google.com</link>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <generator>Zend_Feed</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX 5S - 285 ltr Refrigerator with FREE STEAM IRON &  Ice Twister and Ice Collector.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/whirlpool-m-mind-30-vx-5s-285-ltr-refrigerator-with-free-steam-iron.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX CRY INOX 5S 285 ltr Double Door Refrigerator is equipped with 6th Sense Tower Cooling and 5 Star Rating. It has Cell fresh Crisper Cover, D-Oxidizer, Carry egg Tray, Bottle Holder, Multi Utility Bin, Freezer Compartment, Ice Twister and Ice Collector. The Image given is only for reference purpose and actual colour/looks may vary from the above Image.

Whirlpool M MIND 30 VX CRY INOX 5S 285 ltr Double Door Refrigerator is equipped with 6th Sense Tower Cooling and 5 Star Rating. It has Cell fresh Crisper Cover, D-Oxidizer, Carry egg Tray, Bottle Holder, Multi Utility Bin, Freezer Compartment, Ice Twister and Ice Collector. The Image given is only for reference purpose and actual colour/looks may vary from the above Image.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Whirlpool Plug-and-Play Refrigerator for Kitcheny</li>
<li>Featured above is a geeky refrigerator inviting women who feel handicap to work in kitchen in absence of gadgets.</li>
<li>Serving dual purpose, this Whirlpool Plug-and-Play refrigerator takes you to an altogether different world which is surrounded by gadgets.</li>
<li>The very plug in of this household accessory would put you across an array of gadgets.</li>
<li>Right on the heels of its &lsquo;centralpark&rsquo; feature,</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/n/i/night_lights_people_party_events_2560x1440_wallpaper_www.wallpaperno.com_1_1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Things come alive on the stunning widescreen LED Multi-Touch Apple iPad 2.With WiFi and 3G support, ]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/things-come-alive-on-the-stunning-widescreen-led-multi-touch-apple-ipad-2.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Things come alive on the stunning 9.7-inch widescreen LED Multi-Touch display of the Apple iPad 2. With WiFi and 3G support, this 64GB Apple iPad ensures you stay connected to your world all the time. The built-in dual-core A5 chip in this Wi-Fi + 3G iPad facilitates high-end gaming, surfing and overall performance.
Gaming is at a vivid high with up to nine times the graphics performance on this 64GB Apple iPad. Capture immaculate shots in HD with the 0.7 MP front camera of this Wi-Fi iPad, while the secondary 0.3 MP VGA Camera lets you enjoy FaceTime video calling. For an enhanced movie-watching experience, play all your iPad’s digital content wirelessly on HDTV and speakers using AirPlay. Weighing a mere 1.34 lbs, with an amazing 10-hour battery life, Bluetooth 2.1 + EDR technology and more, this Apple iPad 2 is here to become another extension of you.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every year since 2010, there has been a new version of the iPad. In 2012, we've already seen three. One, the iPad Mini, is a different beast altogether.</p>
<p> The new iPad (technically just known as "iPad" at the Apple Store) has a few upgrades, two minor, one significantly major. A Lightning connector replaces the old 30-pin, just like all other new iOS devices this fall. </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Samsung UN55ES8000F 55" LED TV (1920x1080, 240 Hz, HDTV, 3D) With the LED ES8000, experience the next level.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/samsung-un55es8000f-55-led-tv-1920x1080-240-hz-hdtv-3d.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the LED ES8000, experience the next level of Samsung SMART TV technology. Smart Interaction, with Voice Navigation and Gesture Control, allows you to say commands and control TV functions with your hands, while Face Recognition automatically logs you in to App accounts.
 In addition to finding all your favorite shows and movies, you will be able to enjoy the new Signature Services; Family Story, Fitness, and Kids Story. These features are powered by a Dual Core Processor, along with a Built-in camera for Skype and Signature Services.
The Samsung ES8000 Slim LED TV delivers an outstanding home entertainment experience. You can discover the future of smart TV with Smart Interaction1 (Voice Control Face recognition and Motion Control) as well as Smart Hub2 features like Family Story sharing and AllShare Play3 access to compatible devices. Browse the web2 utilise Samsung Apps2 and chat with Skype®4 built-in. Three USB ports mean you can access multiple files and watch your favourite movies with ConnectShare play and USB PVR5.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50,000:1 Dynamic Contrast Ratio delivers deeper blacks and brighter whites through contrast and dimensions</p>
<p>Hisense LED TVs brings you exceptionally vibrant and true-to-life images delivered just as the director imagined</p>
<p>HDMI combines uncompressed digital audio and video signals into a single cable for high-definition sources</p>
<p>Fast response time generates clear motion scenes.</p>
<p>See a clear picture from anywhere in the room with the wide 178° viewing angle</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sony have introduced the Xperia E as a new entry-level handset with HD Voice plus data and power-saving tools for new smartphone users.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/sony-have-introduced-the-xperia-e-as-a-new-entry-level-handset-with-hd-voice-plus-data-and-power-saving-tools-for-new-smartphone-users.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Xperia E puts one thing above all else, voice calls; a function that obviously predates when the ‘smart’ came to smartphones, but nevertheless, one of the most important features of any phone and something that recent devices have seemed to place on the back burner somewhat. 

The Sony Xperia E is one of the most affordable handsets to feature HD Voice and provided you’re on a network and calling a handset which both support the service, calls are said to be significantly more crystal then what we’ve come to expect from the average phone call, both when speaking and listening.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sony’s new low-cost handset doesn’t simply revolve around HD Voice of course, it also has a full suite of Sony Mobile features, services and apps, not to mention a similar design language to more premium handsets such as the Sony Xperia J and special tools designed to ease those users new to smartphones into the Sony ecosystem.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Break The Limits Of Slim With LG Blade 14.0 (35.8 CMS) HD LED LCD NOTEBOOK. With trendsetting slim styles.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/break-the-limits-of-slim-with-lg-blade-14-0-35-8-cms-hd-led-lcd-notebook-with-trendsetting-slim-styles-that-never-sacrifice-speed-or-power.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[trendsetting slim styles that never sacrifice speed or power, LG laptops have the latest state-of-the-art designs and features. With the best combination of performance for size, 
as well as cutting-edge technology in display and sound that sets new standards in entertainment – LG notebooks and laptops pack a serious 3D punch for 3D games, movies or graphics. Find your laptop or notebook and be sure to see all of our computer products and accessories.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seize your smart style with LG Blade that integrates our slimmests design with new and innovative technologies. Every angle is sliced slimmer from its super slim 4.5mm LED LCD to its 10mm super slim Bezel that’s packed within the metallic 23.8 mm body. The trendsetting slim style never sacrifices speed or power as it offers the best combination of performance or size. Join the slim innovation with the sharp styled LG Blade.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Experience The Superior Sound On The Road.Direct FM/CD Audio Recording to USB Now record your favorite songs]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/experience-the-superior-sound-on-the-road-direct-fm-cd-audio-recording-to-usb-now-record-your-favorite-songs-playing-from-fm.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Easy & Simple Plug and Play. LG Head units have a built-in Front Audio Aux in, for connection to portable music players and other external devices. Just a single connection to make listening more convenient.

Extreme Dynamic Sound System It can increase the low and high range sound so that the listener can experience dynamic powerful sound by simply pushing the XDSS button. In addition, XDSS Plus, which is LG's premium sound effect, gives listeners deeper and stronger low range sound.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You do not need any more annoying cables to listen to music from the smart phones in your car. Just download Wics Apps to your smart phones , and music files in your smart phones will be played from your car speakers.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/delicious-cocktails-don-t-have-to-be-alcoholic-whether-you-re-catering-for-a-guest-who-is-driving-home-or-you-simply-feel-like-something-lighter.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home or you simply feel like something lighter, here are a few recipe ideas for some delicious and healthy non-alcoholic drinks.

Place the blueberries and hulled strawberries in a liquidiser and a little tonic water. Blend until smooth then top up with the remaining tonic water. Serve over ice, if preferred.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>150ml tomato juice</li>
<li>Tabasco sauce</li>
<li>Worcestershire sauce</li>
<li>Fresh lemon juice</li>
<li>Celery salt and pepper</li>
<li>To garnish, a stick of celery and a wedge of lime</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Goods Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
