<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[ Feeds]]></title>
    <link>www.google.com</link>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <generator>Zend_Feed</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ADHD Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder: A child with this disorder will have the same problems.]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Special education deals with children that have special needs. This includes children who are above or below the average of the population. It includes physical and learning disabilities, development, behavioral, and emotional disorders, and gifted and/or talented children.

There are several acronyms for special education that are used in the paperwork involved in the assessment and placement of children with special needs.  Following are some of the most used acronyms.  ]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>VI Visual Impairment: This is simply visual impairment that affects school performance. </li>
<li>TBI Traumatic Brain Injury: This is injury to the brain that results in mental, physical, or behavioral changes. </li>
<li>OI Orthopedic Impairment: OI covers any orthopedic impairment that impedes a child’s education.</li>
<li>OHI Other Health Impaired: This covers health problems that affect the child’s school performance.   </li>
<li>GT Gifted and Talented: This is a child whose abilities are above average intellectually</li>
</ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ A romantic day together at the Fortina Spa, where complete relaxation and luxury is the key to the perfect day]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fortina Spa – The relaxing Spa environment is a complete change from the everyday stress of life and offers total relaxation to release tension, lift the spirit and enhance that ‘feel good’ factor we all crave. Within the vast area of the Spa there are three additional spa facilities namely Spa Sante, Belle Époque Beauty Centre and the Hypogeum all designed to leave you feeling refreshed, revitalised and recharged.

Chinese and Thai Cuisine has won four awards in the last few years. Can Thai at the Fortina Spa Resort uses only the finest quality ingredients brought in from around the world to offer you the most authentic, great tasting dishes on the Island. Can Thai brings together an exquisite combination of Cantonese and Thai cuisine, with very welcoming Asian staff and the tropical ambience of the tropical gardens which surround this restaurant. It’s the ideal place to dine in a romantic setting.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Booking required. 2346 2149
You must state your intention to utilize the voucher on booking
Black out days from 23rd Dec 2012 to 3rd Jan 2013
Cannot be used in conjunction with any other special offer, discount or membership scheme
Beverages are not included in the restaurant
USDA Steaks and Lobster dishes are not included
Parking is not included in this deal
Limited to 25 deals per person
Opening Times:
Fortina Spa Open from 9am – 7pm daily
Spa Sante Open from 2pm – 6pm weekdays and from 10am – 6pm on weekends & public holidays
Taste Open for Lunch from Tuesday to Sunday
Can Thai Open for lunch from Thursday to Tuesday

Limit of 25 deals per person.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Delicious cocktails don’t have to be alcoholic. Whether you’re catering for a guest who is driving home or you simply feel like something lighter, here are a few recipe ideas for some delicious and healthy non-alcoholic drinks.

Place the blueberries and hulled strawberries in a liquidiser and a little tonic water. Blend until smooth then top up with the remaining tonic water. Serve over ice, if preferred.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>150ml tomato juice</li>
<li>Tabasco sauce</li>
<li>Worcestershire sauce</li>
<li>Fresh lemon juice</li>
<li>Celery salt and pepper</li>
<li>To garnish, a stick of celery and a wedge of lime</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Your local Morrisons Pharmacy is a great place to pick up friendly, expert advice for quitting smoking.Your local Morrisons Pharmacy is a great place...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The best plan of action for giving up is to pick a quit date and stick to it. Make sure you have plenty of distractions in place to take your mind off your cigarettes.

Only 3% of smokers are able to stop without the help of pharmacists like ours. We can offer a variety of nicotine replacement options to help you kick the habit.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Reduce the risk of stroke, heart disease and cancer.</li>
<li>Protect people around you from passive smoking.</li>
<li>Save money – one pack of 20 cigarettes a day costs more than £2,000 a year.</li>
<li>Breathing becomes easier and food and drink tastes better.</li>
<li>You’ll look fresher as the tar in cigarettes can stain your skin and teeth.</li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Now it’s even easier to keep track of friends and loved ones. Social tag lets you link the faces in your photo album with their social media...]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharing your content with friends nearby should be easy, quick, and even fun. S Beam lets you bond instantly so you can transfer documents, contacts, pictures, music, videos, Just put the backs of your phones together, connect, share and enjoy.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Pick-up dates: 15 February 2013 - 15 March 2013</li>
<li>Items will be discarded after the validity period for pick-up ends</li>
<li>Pick-up Hours: Mon-Fri: 9.00am - 6.00pm; Sat-Sun: 10.00am - 5.00pm (Excludes National &amp; Federal Territory Holidays</li>
<li>Pick-up Instructions: Please bring the printed confirmation email and valid personal identification</li>
<li>Pick-up from:</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/images/catalog/product/placeholder/thumbnail.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[test deal]]></title>
      <link>http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/index.php/upcoming-deals.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[test deal]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2013 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Main Deal</category>
      <category>Upcoming Deals</category>
      <enclosure url="http://apptha-demo.com/gc/gpc9/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/9df78eab33525d08d6e5fb8d27136e95/r/a/rackmultipart20121227-17749-19k6udn_wide.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="150"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
